JIMAL TAHALAW

WFB DFVFI OPFR

CONTACT



+92-3245383840



wajahatjamil566@gmai

I.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/ wajahat-jamil-33648a 22a/

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Basic JavaScript

Csharp

ASP.NET CORE

MVC

Web API

SOL Server

MS SQL

LANGUAGES

English

Urdu

SUMMARY

🔔 Male | 📥 30th June, 1997 | 🔮 Pakistan, Abbottabad

Citizenship: Pakistan

As a software engineering graduate from Abbottabad University Of Science And Technology, I am currently interning at Cube Health Care as a .NET developer. I have completed an online C# certification and a 2-month front web development course from URRAAN, gaining experience in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and basic JavaScript, My proficiency in programming and strong problem-solving skills make me an asset to any software team.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

.NET Intern

Cube Heathcare Systems Limited

Dec 2022 - May 2023

During my internship as a .Net Developer at Cube Healthcare Systems Limited, I gained practical experience working with ASP.Net Core, MVC architecture, Repository Patterns, Web APIs, and building RESTful APIs that provided access to data from different sources and SQL Server. I also worked on a middleware system that enabled different systems to communicate with each other, providing seamless integration between them. I assisted senior developers in designing and developing software applications. My responsibilities included writing code for different modules of the applications, debugging the code, and ensuring that the applications were running smoothly. This internship provided me with valuable hands-on experience in the healthcare IT industry and the skills necessary to develop innovative solutions.

PHP Developer

WolfsTech

Jun 2022 - Sep 2022

As a PHP Developer at Woltstech, I was responsible for designing the basic front-end designs using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and basic JavaScript and maintaining the back-end using PHP and MySQL. Overall, my experience as a PHP Developer at Woltstech provided me with valuable hands-on experience in web development, including front-end design and back-end maintenance using PHP and MySQL.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Software Engineering

Abbottabad University Of Science And Technology

Sep 2016 - Dec 2020

Pre-Engineering

Government Post Graduate Collage N0#1 Abbottabad

Aug 2014 - Aug 2016

Matriculation

Government High School N0#3 Abbottabad

Apr 2012 - Apr 2014

CERTIFICATIONS

C# Basic

HackerRank

Sep 2022

Learn C Sharp Programming From Scratch

Eduonix

Sep 2022

Certificate In IT (Web, Software & Mobile App. Development)

National Vocational and Technical Training Commission NAVTTC

Feb 2022